export const data = [
  {
    question: "What does MERN stack stand for?",
    options: ["MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js", "MySQL, Express.js, React.js, Node.js", "MongoDB, Angular.js, React.js, Node.js", "MongoDB, Express.js, Ruby on Rails, Node.js"],
    answer: "MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js"
  },
  {
    question: "Which component of the MERN stack is responsible for handling server-side logic?",
    options: ["MongoDB", "Express.js", "React.js", "Node.js"],
    answer: "Node.js"
  },
  {
    question: "Which database is commonly used with the MERN stack for storing data?",
    options: ["MySQL", "SQLite", "MongoDB", "PostgreSQL"],
    answer: "MongoDB"
  },
  {
    question: "Which framework is used for building user interfaces in a MERN stack application?",
    options: ["Angular.js", "Vue.js", "React.js", "Ember.js"],
    answer: "React.js"
  },
  {
    question: "Which part of the MERN stack is used for building the backend API?",
    options: ["React.js", "Node.js", "Express.js", "MongoDB"],
    answer: "Node.js"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the role of Express.js in the MERN stack?",
    options: ["Database management", "Frontend development", "Server-side application framework", "State management"],
    answer: "Server-side application framework"
  },
  {
    question: "Which programming language is primarily used with Node.js in the MERN stack?",
    options: ["Python", "JavaScript", "Ruby", "Java"],
    answer: "JavaScript"
  },
  {
    question: "In MERN stack development, where is React.js commonly used?",
    options: ["Backend", "Frontend", "Database", "API"],
    answer: "Frontend"
  },
  {
    question: "Which module in Node.js is commonly used for interacting with MongoDB in a MERN stack application?",
    options: ["mongoose", "express", "react", "axios"],
    answer: "mongoose"
  },
  {
    question: "Which tool is commonly used to manage dependencies in a MERN stack project?",
    options: ["npm", "yarn", "pip", "composer"],
    answer: "npm"
  }
];
